虚幻勇士冒险 S2E4 灾难 由özberk özen制作
视频来源：https://youtu.be/3Gsn0kq05pw，中文字幕由熙洛Chincode制作，翻译：jky，Albeta
Okay Aelita. Now check the data from William's old tower.
好的 Aelita 现在检查William的旧塔的数据
Roger. Although everything seems normal. Why are we checking the data Daddy?
收到 虽然一切看起来都很正常 但为什么我们要检查爸爸的数据？
To be honest, this is really bazzar.
说实话 这真的很让人头疼
The Super scan detect some kind of strange clone signals, and I don't like this at all
超级扫描器检测到某种奇怪的克隆信号 我一点也不喜欢这个
Signals are coming from the garden of Kadic Academy, Jeremy.
信号来自凯德中学的花园 Jeremy
Would you please notify Odd, Ulrich and Yumi about the situation?
请你把这一情况通知给Odd Ulrich和Yumi
They need to check the garden of course.
当然 他们需要检查花园
The garden of the Academy? Are you sure?
学校的花园？你确定吗？
Yes and signals are too strong. I wonder what is XANA up to now.
是的 而且信号太强了 我想知道XANA现在在做什么
I'm sure we'll find out in no time.
我相信我们很快就会发现的
I hope that too sweatheart. I really hope so.
亲爱的 我也真的希望如此
This is horrible. School is about to start again, and we have to deal with both school and XANA
这真是太可怕了 马上要上课了 我们必须同时处理学校和XANA的问题
It's bad, but you know me I am strong enough to deal with both of them. You'll see.
这很糟糕 但你知道我 我有足够的力量来处理这两个问题 你会明白的
U: Oh wait Jeremy's calling.
哦 等等 Jeremy的电话
Yes, Einstein.
是的 爱因斯坦
Ulrich the super scan receives strange clone signals in the garden of the Academy.
Ulrich 超级扫描器收到了来自学校花园的奇怪克隆信号
Please go check the forest.
请去检查森林
Clone signals. Is there any activity tower on Lyoko?
克隆信号 Lyoko里有什么激活的圆塔吗
Hello, Einstein hello?
喂 爱因斯坦 喂
Ulrich hello. I don't believe this. the connection is down.
Ulrich 喂 难以置信 电话断了
I hope he understood me.
我希望他能听懂我的话
Hey guys, I think something bad is happening.
嘿 伙计们 我想有坏事发生了
Jeremy told me the super scan sense some clone signals in the garden
Jeremy告诉我 超级扫描器在花园里检测到了一些克隆的信号
and he wants us to check the forest.
所以他想让我们去森林里看看
Let's go.
我们走吧
I wonder what is XANA planning for us now.
我想知道XANA现在对我们有什么计划
I hope it's nothing bad. What was that?
我希望这不是什么坏事 那是什么？
Mmm-hmm what is this?
嗯 这是什么？
Okay, okay.
好吧 好吧
This is not good. I seriously don't like this.
这不是好事 我真的不喜欢这个
Einstein. It's a disaster. There is a tower in the garden of the Academy.
爱因斯坦 这是一场灾难 在学院的花园里有一座圆塔
But that's impossible!
但那是不可能的
Then please wake us up because we're all delusional.
那就请从幻想之中叫醒我们
Okay, okay, I get it. come to the factory right now.
好吧 好吧 我明白了 马上到工厂来
Monsters might show up. It's too dangerous, hurry.
怪兽可能会出现 太危险了 快点
Okay? We're on our way, but I have a really bad feeling about this.
好吗？我们在路上了 但我有一种非常不好的感觉
Hello lyoko warriors! miss me?
你好 Lyoko战士们 想我吗？
Wait! is that William?
等等 那是William吗？
Wait how can you teleport here like that?
等等 你怎么能像这样传送到这里？
Let's just say I am special than the others.
只能说我比其他人特别
Well then. I'm sure it will be pleasure to beat you William!
那就好 很高兴我会打败你的 William
You need to be more faster than that Yumi!
你要比他更快才行啊 Yumi
Yumi! dont you dare to touch her!
Yumi！你敢碰她吗？
Take that!
吃吃这个
William no!
William 不要
Did you just...
你刚才……
I did what I have to do.
我做了我该做的
Besides its just the clone. It's not real.
而且 这只是个克隆 不是真的
Odd's right no time to lose. Let's go before he recovers himself.
Odd说得对 没时间了 我们在他恢复之前走吧
Come on.
来吧
Finally you took your time, come on.
你们终于到了 来吧
I want to hear everything about this tower.
我想听听关于这座塔的一切
Without getting into details, we just saw the tower in middle of the forest.
不谈细节 我们只是看到圆塔处在森林中间
That's it.
就这样吧
But how can this even be possible unless wait?
但这怎么可能呢 除非 等等
That's it. XANA moved my tower the one in the north to the Kadic Academy.
就这样 XANA把我在北方的那座塔移到了凯德中学
So you mean this is the tower where you were teleported to earth?
所以你的意思是这就是你那座被传送到地球的圆塔？
Yes, XANA moved the tower to the Kadic Academy.
是的 XANA把圆塔移到了凯德中学
What should we do about this tower than?
那我们应该怎么处理这座圆塔呢？
You need to teleport to earth and destroy this tower for good.
你需要远程传送到地球 并永远地摧毁这座圆塔
Wait with teleport you mean the teleport.
等等 你说的远程传送是指远程传送
I'm thinking about are just it's on the teleport teleporter.
我以为的是在传送器上远程传送
You'll soon find out.
你很快就会知道了
Anyway Jeremy I need your help with the word transfer.
无论如何 Jeremy 我需要你帮我输入传送指令
Of course.
当然了
Okay, let's destroy that Tower.
好吧 让我们摧毁那座圆塔
Aelita is waiting for you all in Sector 5.
Aelita已经在第五空间等着大家了
The virtualization process is about to start.
虚拟化过程即将开始
Lady first.
女士优先
Thank you kindly sir.
谢谢你的好意 先生
Transfer Yumi.
传送Yumi
Transfer Ulrich.
传送Ulrich
Transfer Odd.
传送Odd
Scanner and Virtualization.
扫描 虚拟化
I was getting bored in here alone. Let's go.
我一个人在这里都快闷死了 我们走吧
Wait didn't we have to be connected to a tower on Lyoko to be transferred to earth?
等等 我们不是要连接到Lyoko的圆塔才能被转移到地球吗？
There's no need for that.
没有这个必要了
The tower in the Kadic academy links to lyoko it all.
凯德中学的圆塔与Lyoko连接在一起
We only will need Skid for the transfer.
我们只需要Skid进行远程传送
Okay here we go!
好了 那我们开始吧
Teleportation: Aelita, Odd, Yumi, Ulrich.
远程传送 Aelita，Odd，Yumi，Ulrich
Everything's fine Einstein we're in Kadic right now.
一切都很好 爱因斯坦 我们现在就在凯德中学
Let's go to the tower.
让我们去圆塔
Please everyone, be careful.
请大家小心
Don't worry Einstein we can handle anything.
别担心爱因斯坦 我们能应对任何事
We found the tower.
我们找到了圆塔
Huh, be careful XANA just activate the tower.
恩 小心点 XANA刚刚启动了圆塔
Be aware. I don't like this. I dont like this.
要注意 我不喜欢这样
We will manage, father. Don't worry.
我们会处理好的 父亲 别担心
XANA is using exact same trick.
XANA正在使用同样的伎俩
Didn't I just kill you like 1 hour ago or so.
我不是一小时前才杀了你吗？
That will be never happen dont worry Odd!
那是永远不会发生的 别担心 Odd
Show me what you got lyoko warriors!
让我看看你有什么本事 Lyoko战士们
Laser arrow.
激光箭
Super smoke protection!
超级烟雾保护
Energy field.
能量球
Nice try!
不错的尝试
Aelita be carefull.
Aelita要小心
Get away from her. Now!!
离她远点 就现在
Super sprint! Impact!!
超级冲刺 命中
That'll teach you a lesson, huh.
恩 这会给你一个教训
Hahaha nice work.
哈哈哈 干得好
I'll take care of the tower.
我来处理圆塔
Okay, Aelita, but please I have a request.
好吧 Aelita 但请我有个请求
Find some data about how XANA was able to move the tower.
找到一些关于XANA如何能够移动塔的数据
Okay, daddy.
好的 爸爸
Hang on! Einstein! something is happening.
坚持住 爱因斯坦 有事发生了
Huh? What do you mean?
嗯？你是什么意思?
There are strange lights coming out of the tower.
有奇怪的光从圆塔里出来
What the hell is that. It's like a tornado, or it is even a tornado.
那是什么鬼东西 就像龙卷风 或者说它甚至是龙卷风
What is that? It's going to the sky.
那是什么？它在向天空飞去
To the sky? Oh? No. This is not good.
上天？哦 不 这不是好事